twingly.com 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy — Twingly

Twingly AB (“Twingly”) operates the website twingly.com. It is Twingly’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

 **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Twingly collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Twingly’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Twingly’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Twingly may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Twingly also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on the Twingly blog. Twingly only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Twingly’s websites choose to interact with Twingly in ways that require Twingly to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Twingly gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Twingly are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Twingly collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Twingly. Twingly does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Aggregated Statistics**

Twingly may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Twingly may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Twingly does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Twingly discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Twingly’s behalf or to provide services available at Twingly’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Twingly’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Twingly will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Twingly discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Twingly believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Twingly, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Twingly website and have supplied your email address, Twingly may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Twingly and our products during a period of maximum 24 months from the day you registered unless otherwise agreed. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Twingly takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. If you would like us to not contact you or to be removed from our register, you are welcome to inform Twingly at support@twingly.com and we will meet your request.

If you believe that Twingly is not handling your personal details in a correct manner, please contact Twingly at compliance@twingly.com or inform the correspondent regulatory body in your country.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Twingly uses cookies to help Twingly identify and track visitors, their usage of Twingly website, and their website access preferences. Twingly visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Twingly’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Twingly’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Business Transfers**

If Twingly, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Twingly goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Twingly may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Twingly may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Twingly’s sole discretion. Twingly encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This Privacy Policy has partly been generously shared by our friends at [Automattic](https://automattic.com/).
